[Music]
good day I Alexa D bransky I'm a senior
software engineer on the business
Central team hi my name is jayen topa
I'm also a senior software developer
with the business Central team today I
will share the latest news about the
sales line suggestion with cap
pilot which is a assistant designed to
streamline the creation of sales quotes
orders and invoices using natural
language or structured data it helps
easily add lines to the new sales
documents either from item list or from
previously created
documents thanks to the available
feedback we got and to more powerful
capabilities of kilot we've made several
improvements to the feature to extend
this functionality and to make it work
faster and more
reliable so let me walk you through
these improvements first we've improved
the product search by better keyword
extraction let me Dem how it works now I
have the sales order here and I want to
use a sales line suggestion
feature first I'm asking the cap pilot
about six guest chairs and a couple of
desks and this example I made a mistake
of not having a wi space between guest
and chairs here and let's see how kilot
deals with
this and it did it right it recognizes
that guest chair in in one word actually
means guest and chair in in two words
here and it puts the right quantity to
both items let me give you a couple of
more examples of a context
understanding now I'm asking the kilot
for a small coffee maker let's see what
it
suggests and gives me a small coffee
machine for personal use you can see the
picture right over here but let's
slightly change the query here I need a
bigger coffee
maker now it offers the bigger machine
the third
request I'm giving the cap pilot is I
need a big coffee maker
for commercial
use and that's a big one that I got
here these examples show how cap pilot
understand the context of my queries now
what number two is that product search
now works up to 10 times
faster for for example for a database
with 40,000 items the search time has
decreased from 60 seconds to just 56
seconds let me give you a brief
example here I'm requesting for two
desks black and green chairs six H and
lamps for these
desks I click
generate and I took a system to 3
seconds to give me the results and you
can see that it recognize the context of
these desks and suggest with me two
lamps as I have two desks it gives me
two lamps one lamp for each desks and
six each black and green
chairs the third point is with add the
ability to search for blanket orders as
a source to do as a source document to
copy from and the important thing here
is that it doesn't merely copy from the
blanket order it establishes direct link
to the blanket order line so you won't
exceed quantity in the blanket
order so here I'm typing get items from
the blanket
order previously I have created the
blanket order for this specific customer
we click generate
here and now we retrieve two two lines
from the blanket order and here's the
link to the blanket order then we change
the quantity say five and five insert
these lines into sales
order and then ship the sales
order now if we go to the linked blanket
orders
here we will see our blanket order that
we have linked to and the shipped
quantity our five and five what we
shipped in the sales order we've just
created with the sales line suggestion
feature so I won't be able to ship more
than five for this first item and 10
pieces for the second
item the fourth Point here is we can
narrow the search down to specific
document
in other words you can search items not
from all item list but from the
previously from those items that are
included in the document you specify let
me Demo it how it works in my example I
have a sales quote that contains chair
and a lamp now I'm asking the sales line
for a coffee
machine it works as it should it suggest
me the coffee machine from the item list
then I'm asking a coffee machine from
the sales
quote sq1 is a number of my sales
quote and it give me nothing because I
don't have a coffee machine in the sales
quote let's ask the copilot what do I
have in the sales quote
I can see that in that sales quote I
have a ram chair green and a lamp then
I'm asking the compilot to give me just
shair from the sales
quote and it's adjust me the chair that
I've
chosen next we've added the support of
units of measure now any units of
measure you have set up for your item is
it's piece
bottles kilos pallets it will be all
considered by the sales line suggestion
feature here I'm asking the sales line
feature for coffee beans I need Brazil
which is delivered in either bags or
packs here I'm asking for two bags and
two more
packs and the capil gives me two lines
here one line for two bags and one line
for two pieces which is
fair lastly but the most prominent
feature is we have added the file
support so that you can query SLS with
the structured data and let me hand it
over to chatton who will tell you more
about this new feature thank you Alexi
now I'm going to talk little bit about
uh sales line suggestion from
attachments uh currently we support only
CSV file type and in the future we hope
we'll have support for other file types
as but for now it's only
CSV the whole process of co-pilot you
know generating suggestions from um CSV
file is a twostep process uh in the
first step it uh co-pilot analyzes the
CSV file that has been uploaded and uh
you know and extracts key information
and know information like uh what column
has um product information what column
has information about quantity and unit
of measure and also you know how is the
CSV structured is it U separated or tab
separated you know what is the column
separator basically all this kind of U
key information is extracted and passed
it on to um The Next Step which is uh
paring the CSV based on the extracted
information and calling the fine product
capability that Alexi talked about just
now and at the end you what you see is U
you know sales line suggestions that uh
the co-pilot produces so let me quickly
show you a demo to illustrate uh the
feature all right for the demo I have a
sales quote here which you can see on
the screen um and I have received a CSV
from my customer or or some external
Source I'll upload the CSV and get the
suggestion from the
copilot the CSV that I'll be using U
looks something like this you can see
there's a lot of information in the CSV
including the information that copilot
is interested in which is U item
information quantity and unit of measure
and um yeah those are the information
that will be fetched from the CSV and uh
let's go ahead and upload the CSV so as
usual I'll go to the SE sales line um
action uh where we had added a new U
action called attach using with you can
upload the CSV file so this was the
file so now it's U up being uploaded the
it's going through First Step which is
extracting the key information uh from
the CSV file once once the information
is extracted it it's presented to the
user in a friendly way uh you can see
the copilot detected that the file has a
tap column separator and uh we also have
a list of all the columns from the CSV
and the copilot s for the mapping for
example the column with name itm is
mapped to product meaning it's a product
information uh you know the column
quantities is uh mapped to the quantity
and likewise unit of measure is map to
unit of
measure so this is a session from
co-pilot and of course the user can go
ahead and change these uh
mappings if the user thinks the copilot
got it wrong so user can basically open
um you know the column action and select
the mapping or change the mapping or
reset whatever it's already done to help
the user in this process uh we also have
actions um under column values where
the user can go and check the the the
values that's in the CSV file so this
will help the user to make a more
informed decision about the
mapping so now the user is happy with
all the mapping that has been done uh
then user can go ahead and uh click on
the generate and this takes um it to the
second uh stage which is uh you know
passing the file based on um the
information that we provided and uh
sending it to the fine product uh
feature or capability and getting the
suggestions you can see that um there
were 20 lines in the Cs file and we got
20 sessions and you could also see that
the performance was quite good in
getting reading 20 lines and getting sus
for all 20
lines um from here of course um the user
can
change uh change the quantity you know
unit of measure or you know remove the
line completely or user can always go
back here and change the mappings and
regenerate so once um the user is happy
with the session the user can go ahead
with uh click on the
insert so now it has added all the
things to your sales quote so when you
click on that insert uh action it also
means that the mapping that was used to
generate the the suggestions were
correct in the that case uh we save the
or we cach the mapping against the
column header sorry the CSV header uh
value meaning in the future if a similar
CSV is uploaded with the same um header
structure then the mapping is used from
U from the database where it's cached so
that copilot need not analyze the CSV
again and um go through the whole
process of uh you know generating the
mapping so you can directly load it from
uh uh from the cache so um this what we
wanted to show you um this brings us to
the end of uh this
presentation uh as usual we we love
feedback from you please uh uh get in
touch with us through any of these
channels that you see on the screen and
let us know what you feel about this uh
features and um uh what kind of changes
you'd like to have for this feature u in
in the future so saying that um I would
like to say thank you and have a nice
day thank you